<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">रोग Finder</string>
    <string name="next">Next</string>
    <string-array name="Anxiety Questions" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation">
        <item>Have you been feeling restless like you are unable to sit in one place?
</item>
        <item>
            Have you been concerned about more than one thing?
        </item>
        <item>
            Have you been agitated or tensed?
        </item>
        <item>
            Have you had trouble staying calm?
        </item>
        <item>
            Have you struggled to control feelings of anxiety, agitation or fear?
        </item>
        <item>
            Have you felt ill tempered or moody?
        </item>
        <item>
            Have you panicked about things that might happen to you or the ones closed to you?
        </item>
        <item>Have you been having any irrational fears, from certain things?</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Schitz Questions" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation">
        <item>
Other people unable to see and hear things that I can
        </item>
        <item>
Sometimes I are unable to speak
        </item>

        <item>
It is tough for me to organize and start working on anything
        </item>

        <item>
I believe i have powers that others don't
        </item>
        <item>
Sometimes words don't come out as i intent
        </item>
        <item>
I can hear conversations that others can't
        </item>
        <item>
I can hear other people taking about me
        </item>
        <item>
I feel people are going to harm me
        </item>
        <item>
I sometimes completely lack emotions
        </item>
        <item>
I believe that someone can take charge of my body completely
        </item>
        <item>
Sometimes i am unable to tell if i am having hallucinations
        </item>
        <item>
I can tell whats going on before it happens
        </item>
        <item>
I believe that i can read other people's minds
        </item>
        <item>
Due to these things i am unable to perform daily functions
        </item>


    </string-array>
    <string-array name="PTSD Questions" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation">
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been  ?
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="Depression Questions" tools:ignore="ExtraTranslation">
        <item>
Have you been  having the feeling that you will never find joy in life?</item>
        <item>
Have you been having problems focusing on daily task?        </item>
        <item>
Have you been feeling lethargic or have no energy?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been eating too little for the past few weeks?        </item>
        <item>
Have you been moving less than usual?        </item>
        <item>
Have you been struggling to get sleep ?
        </item>
        <item>
Have you been overly harsh on yourself?

        </item>
        <item>
Have you been feeling low?

        </item>
        <item>
Have you been feeling suicidal or wanting to harm yourself?

        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>